

# CJIES TAN

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

#### Name:

Xi Jie Tan

#### Fmail:

cijies@gmail.com

#### Phone:

+886-978-109-929

#### Website:

https://cjies.com

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Computer Science B.Eng**

National Cheng Kung University Tainan, Taiwan (2010 - 2014) Major in web development and UI design.

#### **Science Class**

Pay Fong High School Melaka, Malaysia (2004 - 2009) Societies: Multimedia Society

#### **SKILLS**

### Web Developement

React, Angular, Ionic, Django, Sass

#### Design

Branding, RWD design, Sketch

# Languages

Mandarin, English, Japanese, Cantonese, Malay

#### **PROFILE**



# HELLO,

my name is CJ, I am a software engineer and web developer with over three years of experience in Taipei. Specializes in front end development with react/redux, angularJS and hybrid application. Loves to write code in high-paced and challenging environment to deliver high-quality and maintainable product.

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Front End Developer

iCHEF Co. Ltd., Taipei

Mar 2016 - Present

- Developed a web CMS application for restaurant POS.
- Designed and coded a large in-house component library for react apps.
- Created a cross-platform deploy tool to deliver products easier and faster.
- Organized Taipei F2E&RGBA meetup every month.
- Participated in many community-organized meetups to sharing experiences and new findings.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Django, Electron, Docker, etc

#### **Front End Engineer**

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Galaxy Software Services, Taipei

- Positioned as main front-end engineer in design team.
- Architectured a common build scripts for web developement.
- Developed Taipei 1999 mobile application (iOS & Android).
- Optimized and tunned web performance in mobile platforms.
- Worked with software developers from different departments to build large software applications.

Tech skills: Ionic, AngularJS, Cordova, Kendo, .net MVC Joined projects: Payroll System, Document System, Government Projects

#### **E-TOP Project Web Designer**

Jun 2013 - Jul 2014

Computer & Network Center NCKU, Tainan

- Designed website UI.
- Customized Kendo framework's stylesheet.

Tech skills: Kendo, Sass, Codelgniter (PHP)